Floyd S. Fierman papers, ca. 1850-1997 (bulk: 1870 - 1970)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series I: New Mexico’s Jewish History
  - Spiegelberg, Flora. (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Excerpt - "Another Civil War Story" (by Flora Spiegelberg).
  - Spiegelberg, Lehman. (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Genealogy of the Spiegelberg family beginning with Lehman Spiegelberg.
    Court proceedings relating to the case of Adelaida Cienfuegos vs. Carrie L. Spiegelberg (November 21, 1905).
    Correspondence from the assistant adjutant general of the Department of New Mexico to the infantry (Santa Fe; February 25, 1858).
    F. Fierman's notes on the Spiegelberg family; particular focus on Lehman and Levi Spiegelberg.
    Correspondence to F. Fierman from Mr. and Mrs. Robert Lippman (March 1982).
    Genealogy of the Spiegelberg family.
    Copy of photographs of Carrie and Lehman Spiegelberg.
    Copy of correspondence from the board of education in the city of New York to Florence Spiegelberg (February 25, 1910).
    Copy of photographs of Carrie, Florence, Cora, Edwin, Lehman, Charles, and Rena (all related in some way to the Spiegelberg family).
    Copy of the annual commencement proceedings of the Loretto Academy -"Our Lady of Light" (Santa Fe, N.M.; Wednesday, June 22, 1892).
    Obituary - "Prominent Importer Dead" (in honor of Lehman Spiegelberg).
    Copy of legal statements in the case of Adelaida Cienfuegos vs. Carrie Spiegelberg (1910).
  - Spiegelberg, Levi and Betty. (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Original correspondence from William E. Kriegsman to F. Fierman (February 18, 1982).
    Correspondence from Ruth Cole to F. Fierman regarding Levi Spiegelberg (January 16, 1983).
    Copy of obituary for Lehman Spiegelberg.
    Copy of advertisement for Spiegelberg Brothers.
    Copy of the report of conditions of the Second National Bank of New Mexico (1873).
    Copy of map of New Mexico settlements (1694-1850).
  - Spiegelberg family reunion. (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Announcements of the Spiegelberg family reunion (May 25 and June 20, 1988).
    Article - (Hillerman, Anne) "Spiegelberg Gathering to Recall Civic Deeds" (July 13, 1988).
    Article - (Wittenauer, Cheryl) "A Gaggle of Relatives Discuss Legacy of Merchant Brothers" (July 17, 1988).
  - Spiegelberg, Solomon. (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Copy of correspondence to Solomon Spiegelberg from the solicitor general of New Mexico (May 6, 1895).
    Two sentence background on Solomon Spiegelberg.
  - Spiegelberg, Willi. (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Article - "Willi Spiegelberg-- A Builder of the Southwest" (by Flora Spiegelberg).
    Copy of the Session Laws of New Mexico (1866-67).
    Copy of a biography of Willi Spiegelberg (author and date unknown).
    Correspondence from Flora Spiegelberg to her great grandson, Willi Spiegelberg.
    Copy of "Great Grandpa Spiegelberg Presents President Lincoln With a Navajo Blanket" (by Flora Spiegelberg).
    Copy of entry on Flora Spiegelberg from the Biographical Encyclopedia of American Jews (1935).
    Copy of "The Ten Commandments of World Peace" (written by Flora Spiegelberg; 1919).
    Biographical sketch on William E. Kriegsman, genealogy of the Kriegsman family, and notes on the Kriegsman family by F. Fierman.
    Correspondence from Charles Meyer to Marjorie Lamber (September 3, 1958).
    Copy of legal document which declares Willi Spiegelberg probate judge for the county of Santa Fe (November 17, 1884).
    Article - "W.I. Spiegelberg Dies on Trip Abroad" (January 19, 1932).
    Copy of legal document which commands Willi Spiegelberg to appear at the court house to testify in a case (May 9, 1868).
    Copy of street map of Santa Fe (date unknown).
    Legal document which declares the organization of the Second National Bank of New Mexico (August 1, 1872).
    Copy of the passport of William Langerman (January 1857).
    Copy of passport application for William Langerman (1856).
  - Spiegelberg wills and testaments. (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Copy of the last wills and testaments of Solomon Jacob Spiegelberg (1898), Lehman Spiegelberg (1888), Emanuel Spiegelberg (1923), Levi Spiegelberg (1906), and Willi Spiegelberg (1909).
    F. Fierman's notes on the wills of Lehman, Solomon Jacob, Levi, and Willi Spiegelberg.
    Copy of excerpts from the Journal of Probate Court (Santa Fe, New Mexico; 1885).
  - Staab family. (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Book excerpt - (Fierman, F.) Rio Grande History: The Staabs of Santa Fe. 1983.
    Genealogy of the Staab family originating from Abraham Staab and Julia Schuster.
    Correspondence from Bettina Lyons to Abraham Chanin regarding the Staab family (February 12, 1990).
    Correspondence from W.A. Keleher to F. Fierman regarding Edward Staab (May 17, 1961).
  - Starr, Mildred. (Box 4, Folder 37)
    Correspondence between Melissa Amado and Mildred Starr regarding genealogical information on the Cohen, Binnard, and Markman families (1995).
    Information on the Binnard and Markman families compiled by Mildred Starr (1995).
    Excerpt - El Paso City Directory (1920, 1921, 1926).
  - Staten, Charna and Frances Williams: Written permission by Charna Staten to participate in the Temple Beth El community history project (1988). (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Stern, Eugene: Article - (Lease, R.) "Eugene J. Stern: Merchant, Farmer, and Philanthropist of Las Cruces, New Mexico" (January 1977). (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Stern family. (Box 4, Folder 40)
    Manuscript from interview with Dell Zuckerman (October 12, 1991). Genealogy of the Stern family.
    Articles on E.J. Stern. Includes obituary and photographs.
    Transcription of the birth certificate of Jeno Stern (August 24, 1897).
    Copy of certification of naturalization of Eugene Stern.
    Naturalization legal documents.
    Transcription of the school report of Jeno Stern (1906).
    Document (possibly written in Hungarian).
  - Strauss ranch: F. Fierman's notes on the Strauss Cattle Company. (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Strouse family: Manuscript which provides biographic information on Morris and Felix Strouse by Muriel Stulz (copy of photograph of the Strouse family included. (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Sutin, Esther. (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Tachiert, Milton. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Manuscript of interview of Mr. and Mrs. Milton Tachiert by Louis Michelson (July 30, 1975).
    Copy of document which states Congregation Montefiore dues (Las Vegas; 1886).
    Copy of correspondence from F. Fierman to Rabbi Leonard (Helma?) regarding direct and indirect deed indices for various pioneer families in New Mexico (July 26, 1980).
    Correspondence from F. Fierman to Mr. Taichert regarding Congregation Montefiore rabbis from 1886-1931 (January 5, 1981).
    Correspondence from Jacob Marcus to F. Fierman regarding the Schor and Bernstein families (January 15, 1981).
    F. Fierman's notes on Milton Taichert (Las Vegas, New Mexico).
    Correspondence from the comptroller of the currency to F. Fierman regarding information on the San Miguel National Bank in Las Vegas, New Mexico (November 14, 1980).
    Obituary for Milton Taichert submitted by David Scholder (March 14, 1989).
    Article - "The Covenant in New Mexico-1870."
    Obituary for Milton Taichert.
  - Temple Beth El (Las Cruces). (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Newsletters - Temple Beth El Newsletter (December 1994; January-December 1995; January-April 1996; Sept.-Oct. 1996; Nov.-Dec. 1996; April 1997; August 1997; September, 1997).
    List of photographs from Temple Beth El.
    Manuscript - "Temple Beth El of Las Cruces, New Mexico: The Early Years" (by J. P. Brown).
  - Temple Beth Shalom (Santa Fe): Pamphlet - "Faith In the Future" (distributed by Temple Beth Shalom). (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Travel in New Mexico: Article - (Milstein, T.) "Tours Give People Glimpse of Jewish Life In New Mexico" (November 1996). (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Uhlfelder, Emil and Johanna. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    F. Fierman's manuscript notes on the Uhlfelder family.
    Brief biography and inventory of the Blatt and Uhlfelder papers in special collections at the University of New Mexico's Zimmerman Library.
    Copy of correspondences between Morris Blatt and Albert Stern with regard to banking (1938).
    Copy of correspondence from Robert Sundel (from the Transmigration Bureau of the American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, Inc.) to Morris Blatt with regard to a refund (August 22, 1941).
    Copy of the minutes of the board of directors meeting (1930); minutes from anual meeting of stockholders (1931); and special meetings (1938) for Blatt Inc.
    Copy of indentures between the Seligman brothers and Morris and Johanna Blatt (1930, 1933, 1934, 1935, 1936).
    Copy of memorandum of agreement between the First National Bank of Santa Fe and Blatt Inc. (July 1, 1938).
    Copy of receipts issued to Johanna and Morris Blatt from the Rosenwald Brothers (1925-1955).
    Copy of memoranda of verbal agreement between Johanna Blatt and S. Floersheim.
    Copy of receipts and bills issued to Morris and Johanna Blatt from Floersheim Mercantile Co., Morris Gottlieb, Standard Felt Company, El Paso Herald, and Fletcher Catron (1916-1936).
    Copy of the list of the persons in the collection district of New Mexico who paid a tax on incomes of $1,000,000 or more for the year of 1868.
    Article - (Love, Marian F.) "Vignette, Pauline Pollock" (April 1981).
    Article - "Johanna Blatt, Styling Pioneer" (May 7, 1960).
    Brief transcription from the U.S. Surveyor General of the Santa Fe population in 1876.
    Copy of the certificate of naturalization for Johanna Blatt (March 24, 1919).
    Copy of the certificate of registration for Johanna Blatt (July 20, 1918). Includes photograph and thumb print of Johanna Blatt.
    Copy of license from the city of Santa Fe, New Mexico for Johanna Blatt's store (January 1, 1928).
    Copy of correspondence from the Republican State Central Committee to Morris Blatt (October 20, 1928).
    Copy of correspondence from Mrs. Barnett W. Petchesky in regard to a model tenement house which was being built in New York by Mr. Rockefeller, Jr. (December 24, 1924).
  - Villa, Pancho. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Article - "Pancho Villa and the Attack on Columbus, New Mexico" (by Friedrich Katz ).
    Article - "Villa Raided New Mexico Town to Forestall Deal" (by G. Silva; June 27, 1991).
    Article - (Singer, Mark) "La Cabeza de Villa" (November 27, 1989).
  - Woods, Evy: Article - (Zimmerman, Rebecca) "Hidden Children' Coming Out At Last" (September 1991). (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Wormser, Dorothy: Article - "First Jewish Lady Architect of the West: A Picture Story" (October 1984). (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Zielonka, Rabbi Martin: Book excerpt - (Rochlin, Fred and Harriet) Pioneer Jews. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Zimmerman, Cynthia: Article - "Judaic Shop to Open in Old Town" (September 1996). (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Series II: Western Texas' Jewish History
  - Aaronson Brothers. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Newspaper clipping entitled "Aaronson Bros. 2nd Great Birthday Sale."
    Biography and genealogy of the Aaronson brothers (by Floyd Fierman).
    Clipping - "Aaronson Cites Increase Sales."
  - Alfman, Harry. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Genealogy of Lena and Sidney Alfman.
    Biography and genealogy of the Alfman family (1982).
  - Amstater family. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Genealogy of the Amstater family compiled by F. Fierman.
    History of the Amstater family by M. Amstater (1981).
  - Angerstein, Ernest. (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Letter - Dr. B. Sacks to F. Fierman (1961).
    Handwritten notes from the Sacks collection at the Arizona Historical Foundation.
    Handwritten manuscript by B. Sacks with regard to Ernest Angerstein.
    Discussion of the military record (1852-1857) of Ernest Angerstein by B. Sacks.
    "Ernest Angerstein: Soldier, Merchant, Accused Secessionist, and Post Trader" (by F. Fierman).
    Notes on Ernest Angerstein compiled by B. Sacks.
    Letter - Leo R. Schuster to the Army Records Center (August 30, 1961).
    Letter - from the chief quartermaster of New Mexico to General J.H. Carleton (February 10, 1864).
    Letter - Veterans Administration to Leo Schuster (September 28, 1961).
    Letter - E. Angerstein to Lieutenant Col. Nelson H. Davis (December 28, 1863).
    Transcription of announcement on the oath of allegiance taken by E. Angerstein (April 1863).
    Transcription of several oaths of allegiance by E. Angerstein (1863).
    Transcription of affidavit made by J.P. Deus (Las Cruces; Dec. 29, 1863).
    Report - Gen. J. H. Carleton to Adj. Gen. on a corn contract of Angerstein (February 1864).
    Letter - Headquarters Dept. of New Mexico to Col. G W. Bowie (June 6, 1864).
    Letter - E. Angerstein to E.M. Stanton, Secretary of War (June 29, 1864).
    Letter - Chief Quartermaster's Office (Mesilla) from S. Archer (December 24, 1863).
    Transcription of several statements in regard to the loyalty of E. Angerstein (December 1863).
    Transcription of contract between Angerstein and the U.S. military (1863).
    F. Fierman’s notes on Ernest Angerstein.
    Segment of R.C. Colton's The Civil War in the Western Territories... (1959).
    Warranty deed: Cunniffes with Angerstein and H. Lisinsky (Aug. 20, 1872).
    Information on Ernest Angerstein (handwritten by F. Fierman).
    Letter - MNM to F. Fierman regarding E. Angerstein's residence during the Civil War (May 31, 1961).
  - Arizona Rough Riders. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Ashkenaz family. (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Genealogy of the Ashkenaz family.
    Brief history of the Ashkenaz family (transcribed by F. Fierman; February 1983).
  - Backer, Labon and Clara. (Box 5, Folder 17)
    "Grandfather's Essay" (by E. Backer; April 1967; 11 pages).
    Statement prepared by L. Backer (April 1982; 4 pages) on the history of the Backer family.
    Genealogy of the Backer family.
    Article - "One of a Kind Video Programs."
    Letter - David Backer to F. Fierman (March 1982).
  - Baker family. (Box 5, Folder 18)
    History of family (written by C. Baker; 96 pp.), photographs, maps, and genealogies.
    Ketubah (wedding contract) between Baer and Eltzbacher (1807, in Hebrew).
    List of wedding gifts (1799; in Hebrew).
  - Bellman family. (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Eulogy for Samuel Bellman.
    Genealogy of the Bellman family.
  - Berg, Sol I. (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Notes on Berg family history (includes a brief genealogy).
    Poem entitled "Daddy" (by Sol I. Berg).
    Biography of Sol I. Berg.
    "Quinta Berg Built By Bookers on Spanish Land Grant at Ysleta."
    Obituaries for Sol I. Berg (1935).
  - "Billy the Kid." (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Letter - Mrs. Solis Cohen, Mrs. Richard White, to F.Fierman.
    "Billy the Kid, the Cowboy Outlaw ...recalled by Flora Spiegelberg," by F.Fierman.
    Review of F.Fierman article, "Billy the Kid...."
  - Blaugrund, J.B. and Arthur. (Box 5, Folder 22)
    Letter - Isadore Kahn to F. Fierman regarding Blaugrund family history.
    Genealogy and notes pertaining to the family.
    "J.B. Blaugrund" by F.Fierman.
    Article - ( El Paso Herald Post) "Retirement is No Good, Says Busy Executive, 70."
    Copy of "The American Success Story" (by Michael Fones; March 7, 1982).
  - Bloch, Herman. (Box 5, Folder 23)
    Fierman's notes on the Bloch family.
    Article - "Judge Goes 'Easy' on Ex-Con."
    Legal documents (case of Herman Bloch vs. The United States; April 22, 1936).
  - Blum, Isaac: Fierman's notes on Isaac Blum. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Blumenthal family. (Box 5, Folder 25)
    Letter - F.Fierman to Karl Blumenthal (November 9, 1950).
    Biography of Bernhardt Blumenthal (b. 1856).
    Obituaries for Adolph Blumenthal who died at the age of 84.
    Obituary for Sam Blumenthal in the El Paso Times (July 22, 1937).
    Obituary for Pauline Ullman Blumenthal in the El Paso Times (June 23, 1939).
    Obituary for Bernard Blumenthal in the El Paso Times (January 20, 1940).
    Genealogy of the Blumenthal family.
  - B'nai Abraham Synagogue (Brenham). (Box 5, Folder 26)
    "History of B'nai Abraham Synagogue" (by Mrs. Sam Toubin).
    Discussion of B'nai Abraham Synagogue.
  - B'nai B'rith (El Paso). (Box 5, Folder 27)
    Pamphlet produced for the Golden Anniversary of the El Paso B'nai B'rith Lodge 509 (1901-1951).
    Correspondence to members in regard to donations and future meetings (1960-62).
    B'nai B'rith Voice (official publication for the District Grand Lodge No. 7 of B'nai B'rith).
    Article - "Lodge Sponsors Tests for Brain Injuries."
    Three El Paso Jewish Community Center certificates of recognition.
    National Jewish Monthly (July-August, 1961; by B'nai B'rith).
    Article which discusses information on research on brain injuries.
  - Bonem/Goldenberg families: Letter - J.W. Bonem to F.Fierman (August 29, 1980). (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Borschow/Herskowitz families. (Box 5, Folder 29)
    Genealogy of the Borschow family.
    Family history of the Borschows written by descendants.
  - Bromberg, Joseph Hillel: Anonymous handwritten notes which provide background on the Bromberg family. (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Brownsville, TX: Article which discusses interaction between Jews and Blacks in Brownsville. (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Brunschwig, Dr. Alexander. (Box 5, Folder 32)
    F.Fierman's notes on the Brunschwig family.
    Obituary for M. Coblentz (president of the White House Department Store).
    Obituary for Arthur Coblentz (in the El Paso Times; Oct. 7, 1943).
    Obituary for Dr. Alexander Brunschwig ( New York Times; date unknown).
    Letter - Robert Adams to Wilfrid Kransthor (May 17, 1984).
  - Calisher family. (Box 5, Folder 33)
    Genealogy of the Rosenwasser/Calisher families.
    Clippings about the 75th and 80th birthday for Ada Calisher, as well as her obituary.
    Family history of the Calisher/Rosenwasser family.
    Photographs - one is of Jacob Calisher; one is of Ada F. Calisher.
    Articles pertaining to the business of J. Calisher.
    Photograph of a Calisher home (923 N. Oregon St., El Paso; June 19, 1907).
  - Cherno family. (Box 5, Folder 34)
    Genealogy and family history of the Cherno family.
    "Merchant Joe Cherno Dead at 88," El Paso Times (March 5, 1980).
    Obituary for Joe Cherno.
  - Chomer Family. (Box 5, Folder 35)
    Fanny Chomer's autobiography (December 1982). Includes genealogy.
    Correspondence from Fanny Chomer to F.Fierman (Nov. 22, 1982 and February 7, 1983).
    Portions of Fanny Chomer's autobiography which was published by F.Fierman.
    Fierman's notes on the Chomer family (includes genealogy).
    Oral history of Fanny Chomer (February/March 1979).
  - Cohen, Andy and Syd. (Box 5, Folder 36)
    Articles about Syd Cohen's baseball history (by Abe Canin; 1950-1); in the Arizona Daily Star.
    "Name Honors El Paso Baseball Pioneers." (December 27, 1989).
    "El Paso's Cohen Selected for Coaches' Hall." (January 4, 1981).
    "El Pasoans Pour Love on 'The Old Left-hander.'" (May 26, 1981).
    F.Fierman's notes which provide a log of Andy and Syd Cohen's career.
    F.Fierman's manuscript about Andy Cohen.
    "Andy Cohen: El Paso's 'Mr. Baseball.'"
  - Cohen, Rabbi Henry; Biography of Rabbi Henry Cohen (includes photographs). (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Cohen, Rubin: Oral history of Rubin Cohen (February/March 1979). (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Cohn, Richard: Article - (Turner, Virginia) "Pet Rooster Better than Watchdog," El Paso Herald-Post. (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Colton, Ralph F.: Copy of pages 187-198 of The Jewish Experience In America (ed. by Abraham Karp). (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Congregation B'nai Zion (El Paso). (Box 5, Folder 41)
    Original invitation to the ground-breaking of the new building (May 17, 1981).
    Article - (Henry, Pat) "The Unveiling of a New Tradition," El Paso Times (Oct. 22, 1983).
    "A New Synagogue," The El Paso Jewish Voice; vol.10, no.1.
    Newsletters from the sisterhood of B'nai Zion.
    Program for the building dedication of Congregation B'nai Zion.
    Program for the 75th anniversary of Congregation B'nai Zion (1975).
    Booklet which provides financial and architectural information on the new building (1983).
  - Dallas Jewry: Article - "Inside the Jewish Establishment" (November 1975). (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Dreben, Sam. (Box 5, Folder 43)
    Article - "The Fighting Jew" (by Art Leibson).
    Note on Sam Dreben.
    F.Fierman's notes on Sam Dreben.
  - Eger, Albert and Edy. (Box 5, Folder 44)
    Discussion of the ancestry of Albert Eger.
    Article - (Klusmann, Linda) "Is She Victim or Survivor?," El Paso Herald-Post ( June 10, 1982).
  - Elion Family. (Box 5, Folder 45)
    Article - "Early Merchant," El Paso Herald-Post (March 1978).
    Genealogy of the Elion family (June 10, 1982).
    Copy of last will and testament of Isedor Elion (Jan. 9, 1979).
  - El Paso, TX. (Box 5, Folder 46)
    Official souvenir program of the El Paso County Centennial (December 1-3, 1950).
    Program for the centennial celebration.
    Articles which discuss El Paso and its history (originals and copies).
    Article - "'In the Beginning' The Jewish Community...," by F. S. Goodman (1970).
    Manuscript - "There's Jewish Life Outside of New York" (by H. Burnham).
    The Trail of History of El Paso County (Provides map and historical data on El Paso County).
  - El Paso (cemetery records). (Box 5, Folder 47)
    Copy of Concordia Cemetery records (1873-1950).
    F.Fierman's notes taken from the Concordia Cemetery records.
  - El Paso (city directory): Notes from the El Paso city directory, (1888-1900; 1909-1910). (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - El Paso Jewry. (Box 5, Folder 49)
    Article - "El Paso at the Turn of the Century" (by Irving S. Schwartz).
    Clippings which discuss Jewish pioneers in El Paso (with photographs).
  - El Paso (synagogues): Brief discussion of synagogues of El Paso. (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - El Paso Daily Times: F.Fierman's notes taken from the El Paso Daily Times for the year 1900. (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Epstein. Dr. I.M.: Discussion of belief in God between Epstein and F.Fierman; other writings by Epstein. (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Erlich, Jake (name changed to Jack Earle). (Box 5, Folder 53)
    Poster advertising Jack Earle and the Roma Wine Company (1943-44).
    Article - "Giant Plagued By Few Problems, Even Food Rationing is No Bother" (1944).
    Articles and photographs on Jack Earle ("tallest man in the world" - 8 feet 6 1/2 inches tall).
    Announcement from the Roma Wine Co. invitation to join Jack Earle at a wine tasting.
    Copy of "The Long Shadows....." (by Jack Earle; 1952). Includes poems.
    Letter - Julius M. Klein to F.Fierman regarding Jack Earle (August 11, 1981).
  - Feinberg family. (Box 5, Folder 54)
    Brochure for Eppsco (El Paso Pipe and Supply Co.; 1960).
    Annual reports from Enerserv Products Inc.(1981,1982).
    Newspaper articles on the Feinberg family from the El Paso Times (1981-82).
    Program of Fiddler on the Roof in which Izzy and Sara Feinberg were honored.
    Genealogy and notes on the Feinberg family taken by F.Fierman.
    Manuscript which provides a brief biography of Izzy and Sara Feinberg.
  - Feinberg, Sigmund M. (Box 5, Folder 55)
    Letters - Frances Kallison to Rabbi Jacob Marcus.
    Letters - Frances Kallison and F.Fierman (June 11, 1988).
  - Feldman family. (Box 5, Folder 56)
    Letter - Fannie F. Schaenen and Jacob Feldman to F.Fierman (1981).
    F.Fierman's notes on the Feldman family.
    Obituary for David Daniel Feldman.
  - Fertel, Don. (Box 5, Folder 57)
    Item which discusses Don Fertel - a real estate operator and land manager in El Paso.
    History of Don Fertel's family (by Don Fertel).
  - Fierman, Floyd (1 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 59)
    Excerpts: Guts and Ruts: The Jewish Pioneer on the Trail in the American Southwest.
    "Blintzes and Flautas, Kabbala and Cost Codes" (by F.Fierman; 1980).
    Obituary for Fierman.
    Fierman's vita (1969).